(Howard:)How much time do we have?
(Leonard:)Uh, T-minus five hours,
37 minutes to onset of meteor shower.
(Raj:)Okay, our position
is 34.48 degrees north, 118.31 west.
(Raj:)That means the azimuth
should be 168.22 degrees...
(Raj:)...relative to magnetic north
with an elevation of 49.93.
(Howard:)-Anything yet?
-Uh, we have a signal...
-...but no frame lock.
-Hang on. How about now?
[JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING]
We did it. Ha, ha.
We have the West Coast feed of HBO.
(Howard:)Ooh, Real Sex.
(Raj:)Big deal. Every time I watch that...
(Raj:)...it's old women putting condoms
on cucumbers.
(Sheldon:)All right,
let's see what's on the East Coast feed.
(Leonard:)Oh, hey. Dune.
(Raj:)Not a great movie,
but look at that beautiful desert.
(Leonard:)Too bad Sheldon couldn't come with us.
It's just not the same without him.
[ALL LAUGHING]
LEONARD:
That was good. That was good.
[HOWARD & LEONARD SIGH]
(Howard:)Oh, this sucks.
I'm switching back to Real Sex.
(Sheldon:)Sheldon's log.
(Sheldon:)Stardate 63345.3.
(Sheldon:)While my colleagues are off
observing the Leonid meteor shower...
...I've remained behind
to complete my paper...
(Sheldon:)...on the decays
of highly excited massive string states.
(Sheldon:)Although my research is going well...
(Sheldon:)...I do miss the warmth
of human companionship.
[LAUGHS]